module.exports = [
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "You may pass another vehicle on its left-hand side if: (i) that the vehicle indicates that it is going to turn right and the road is wide enough for you to pass him without needing to drive on the shoulder of the road; (ii) the road has two traffic lanes in the same direction; (iii) if a police officer orders you to do so",
    options: [
      "All of the above are correct",
      "(iii) only is correct",
      "(ii) and (iii) only are correct"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above are correct"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the general speed limit in urban areas?",
    options: ["60 km/h", "80 km/h", "100 km/h", "120 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: "60 km/h"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Your vehicle's headlights must be switched on: (i) at any time of the day when you cannot see persons and vehicles 150 m in front of you; (ii) from sunset to sunrise; (iii) when it rains and you cannot see vehicles 100 m in front of you",
    options: [
      "(ii) only is correct",
      "(i) and (ii) only are correct",
      "All the above are correct"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All the above are correct"
  },
  
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "You must yield to oncoming traffic if you want to turn right",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: "True"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Vehicles have the right of way over pedestrians",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: "False"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "You can use a stop sign as a yield",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: "False"
  },
  
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "When must you stop at a stop sign?",
    options: ["Only if other vehicles are present", "Always", "Only at night", "Only if pedestrians are present"],
    correctAnswer: "Always"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the speed limit, unless otherwise indicated by a regulatory sign for mini buses conveying passengers on a freeway?",
    options: ["80 km/h", "120 km/h", "100 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: "100 km/h"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the general speed limit on urban roads unless otherwise indicated by a regulatory sign?",
    options: ["40 km/h", "60 km/h", "80 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: "60 km/h"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What speed limit, unless otherwise indicated by a regulatory sign for vehicle combination with a GMV/GCM over 9000kg on a freeway?",
    options: ["80 km/h", "100 km/h", "90 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: "90 km/h"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the speed limit for buses and mini buses conveying passengers outside an urban area?",
    options: ["100 km/h", "120 km/h", "80 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: "100 km/h"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the general speed limit on national roads?",
    options: ["100 km/h", "80 km/h", "120 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: "100 km/h"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the general speed other than a town or city not indicated by a road sign?",
    options: ["60 km/h", "80 km/h", "100 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: "100 km/h"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Under which conditions will you be allowed to drive a motor vehicle on a public road once you have passed your learners?",
    options: [
      "The person should be seated next to you or directly behind you if he/she cannot sit next to you.",
      "The person should be seated at the seat of the left hand drive.",
      "You must drive under the supervision of a person in possession of a valid driver's license for the same category vehicle that you intend to drive."
    ],
    correctAnswer: "You must drive under the supervision of a person in possession of a valid driver's license for the same category vehicle that you intend to drive."
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "How far may you reverse your vehicle?",
    options: ["500 metres", "200 metres", "As far as it is safe to do so"],
    correctAnswer: "As far as it is safe to do so"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "You may drive through an amber traffic light when:",
    options: [
      "There is no time for an emergency stop",
      "There is no traffic at the intersection",
      "Your vehicle is already over the stop line"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Your vehicle is already over the stop line"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "When is it compulsory to stop your vehicle?",
    options: [
      "When signaled to do so by a scholar patrol",
      "When your vehicle has been in an accident",
      "When signaled to do so by a traffic officer",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What must you do if you have missed the exit on a freeway?",
    options: [
      "Reverse to the turn off",
      "Make a U-turn and go back",
      "Carry on until you can safely exit the freeway by means of another exit"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Carry on until you can safely exit the freeway by means of another exit"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "You are driving a light motor vehicle. Who is exempt from using a seatbelt?",
    options: [
      "Elderly people",
      "Someone with a medical letter or someone who is reversing",
      "Children under the age of 14 years"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Someone with a medical letter or someone who is reversing"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What documents should you always carry in your vehicle when driving?",
    options: ["ID or passport", "Drivers or learners licence", "Birth certificate"],
    correctAnswer: "Drivers or learners licence"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "You want to turn left at an intersection. Which procedures should be followed?",
    options: [
      "Having indicated your intention, wait for crossing pedestrians and keep as close as possible to the left hand side of the road",
      "Indicate your intention, indicate to pedestrians to wait and turn left",
      "Indicate your intention and cut through if other traffic takes too long"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Having indicated your intention, wait for crossing pedestrians and keep as close as possible to the left hand side of the road"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Which statement is false as far as the general duties you may:",
    options: [
      "Not allow passengers to get on or off the vehicle while moving",
      "Not run the engine if it is giving excessive smoke or fumes",
      "Leave the engine running while fuel is being pumped into the vehicle"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Leave the engine running while fuel is being pumped into the vehicle"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Under which circumstances may you not let your engine run?",
    options: [
      "While you are sitting in the driver's seat and talking to a friend in front of his/her house",
      "While you are waiting at a traffic light",
      "While you are filling up fuel"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "While you are filling up fuel"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "A learner driver of a heavy motor vehicle:",
    options: [
      "Is not allowed to drive on a freeway",
      "Must have someone with him/her who has a driver's licence of the same code and a professional driving permit",
      "Is not allowed to drive faster than 60km/h"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Must have someone with him/her who has a driver's licence of the same code and a professional driving permit"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the distance it takes a heavy vehicle to stop is:",
    options: [
      "Short if it is heavy loaded",
      "Shorter on a wet road than on a dry road",
      "Longer if the vehicle is travelling at a high speed"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Longer if the vehicle is travelling at a high speed"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Which of the following can be regarded as abandoned vehicles?",
    options: [
      "A vehicle whose owner cannot be identified",
      "A vehicle that is parked illegally",
      "A vehicle that is likely to cause an obstruction",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "The flat raised hand of a traffic officer means:",
    options: ["Slow down", "Proceed with caution", "Stop"],
    correctAnswer: "Stop"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the function of regulatory sign?",
    options: [
      "They control and direct traffic",
      "They warn of potential hazards",
      "They serve as navigational aids"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "They control and direct traffic"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Your goods vehicle has broken down in a public road. You must display an emergency triangle at least......metres behind the vehicle",
    options: ["20m", "30m", "45m"],
    correctAnswer: "45m"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "You intend moving forward from a parked position, you must:",
    options: [
      "Put on your head lamps",
      "Put on your indicator and warn other road users",
      "Put on your hazard lamps"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Put on your indicator and warn other road users"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "You are approaching a pedestrian crossing. How must one react?",
    options: [
      "Give way to pedestrians who are crossing",
      "You do not have to give way to pedestrians who are waiting to cross",
      "Slow down and hoot"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Give way to pedestrians who are crossing"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "The dipped beams of a motor vehicle should:",
    options: [
      "Be used in urban areas and dense traffic",
      "Be used in rural areas and dense traffic",
      "Be used between sunrise and sunset"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Be used in urban areas and dense traffic"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Abandoned vehicles may:",
    options: [
      "Not to be removed by anyone",
      "Be removed and impounded by a traffic officer",
      "Be removed by passerby who feel that it is likely to be cause of danger"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Be removed and impounded by a traffic officer"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is a blind spot?",
    options: [
      "An advertisement on a bill board",
      "Someone is waving at you",
      "Something that you cannot see on your mirror"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Something that you cannot see on your mirror"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "When you see road marking --- on the road, you must:",
    options: [
      "Drive on the painted island to allow others to pass",
      "Not drive or stop on the painted island",
      "Only overtake in this area"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Not drive or stop on the painted island"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Your vehicle breaks down on a freeway. What must you do?",
    options: [
      "Put your hazards lamps on",
      "Get your vehicle as far off the road as possible",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "You may park:",
    options: [
      "On a two way road that is narrower than 5.6 metres in an urban area",
      "On a traffic island",
      "10 metres away from an intersection"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "10 metres away from an intersection"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "The chevron --- with the arrow heads pointing outwards shows:",
    options: [
      "That there is a boom barricade",
      "That the road is closed at this point",
      "The position of the adjoining road at a T-junction"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The position of the adjoining road at a T-junction"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "There are certain conditions to prevent you from obtaining a licence. They are:",
    options: [
      "You already have a licence of the same class of vehicle",
      "You have been previously disqualified by a court of law and this disqualification is still in force",
      "Your licence has been suspended temporarily and the suspension has not yet expired",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Which of the following actions are compulsory?",
    options: [
      "Set the hand brake before leaving",
      "Switch your head lamps on at 15h30 in the winter",
      "Give right of way to elderly drivers"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Set the hand brake before leaving"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "You are allowed to unfasten your seat belt while reversing, this statement is:",
    options: ["False", "True only in certain situations", "True"],
    correctAnswer: "True"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Are you, as the driver of the vehicle responsible for ensuring that all passengers wear seat belts?",
    options: [
      "Yes, you must ensure that all passengers wear seat belts",
      "No, you are not responsible",
      "No, you must ensure that children under 14 years wear seat belts. Adults are responsible for themselves"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Yes, you must ensure that all passengers wear seat belts"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "There is a fire hydrant on the sidewalk. Where are you allowed to park?",
    options: [
      "1-5 metres away or either side of the hydrant",
      "Adjacent to the hydrant",
      "1 metre away or either side of the hydrant"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "1-5 metres away or either side of the hydrant"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "You are approaching traffic lights. The red disc light is flashing, this means that you must:",
    options: [
      "Slow down",
      "Proceed with caution",
      "Stop as a four way stop and yield to pedestrians and move in sequence as you stopped"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Stop as a four way stop and yield to pedestrians and move in sequence as you stopped"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "When may you overtake on the left?",
    options: [
      "When it is safe to do so and the vehicle you are passing is turning right",
      "When a vehicle has stopped at a pedestrian crossing",
      "When your view is not obstructed"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "When it is safe to do so and the vehicle you are passing is turning right"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "When you are towing a vehicle, the maximum distance that the two vehicles can be apart is:",
    options: ["2 metres", "5 metres", "3.5 metres"],
    correctAnswer: "3.5 metres"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "The seat belts have been removed from your vehicle. Which rule is applicable here?",
    options: [
      "The vehicle may be used on a public road until you get them replaced",
      "The rules does not apply for vehicles older than two years",
      "The vehicle may not be used on a public road"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The vehicle may not be used on a public road"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What must you do at the entrance of a tunnel?",
    options: [
      "Switch on your lamps and proceed through the tunnel with your bright beams on",
      "Switch on your head lamps and dim the beam",
      "Switch on your parking lamps"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Switch on your head lamps and dim the beam"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "You are not allowed to drive or sit in the driver's seat of your private motor vehicle while the engine is running if you have a concentration of alcohol in your blood of:",
    options: [
      "0.05 grams alcohol per 100ml blood or more",
      "0.02 grams alcohol per 100ml blood or more",
      "0.06 grams alcohol per 100ml blood or more"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "0.05 grams alcohol per 100ml blood or more"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "These vehicles are allowed on a freeway:",
    options: [
      "Motorcycles 50cc or less",
      "Minibus, heavy motor vehicles, and motorcycles 125cc or more",
      "Tractors doing freeway maintenance, buses, and light motor vehicles"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Tractors doing freeway maintenance, buses, and light motor vehicles"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the maximum distance that goods may project to the rear of the vehicle?",
    options: ["1.5 metres", "1.8 metres", "2 metres"],
    correctAnswer: "1.5 metres"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What are the rules for carrying passengers in a drawn vehicle?",
    options: [
      "The drawn vehicle must be a semi-trailer",
      "The vehicles must not exceed a speed of 40km/h",
      "The drawn vehicle must be a trailer"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The vehicles must not exceed a speed of 40km/h"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "The furthest you may reverse your vehicle is:",
    options: ["150 metres", "180 metres", "As far as it is safe to do so"],
    correctAnswer: "As far as it is safe to do so"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the minimum age that is required to obtain a learners licence for a light motor vehicle, mass of which does not exceed 3500kg, and for what period of time is this licence valid?",
    options: [
      "10 years, 18 months",
      "17 years, 24 months",
      "17 years, twelve months"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "17 years, 24 months"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "When a vehicle is being towed the driver must have:",
    options: [
      "Efficient brakes",
      "Both efficient brakes and a licence of the same class vehicle that is being towed",
      "Have a licence of the same class vehicle that is being towed"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Both efficient brakes and a licence of the same class vehicle that is being towed"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "If you have learned you can:",
    options: [
      "Drive on the freeway with a licensed driver",
      "Carry passengers",
      "Both drive on the freeway with a licensed driver and carry passengers"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Both drive on the freeway with a licensed driver and carry passengers"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "How often must you look in your mirrors?",
    options: ["10-15 seconds", "5-8 seconds", "20-30 seconds"],
    correctAnswer: "5-8 seconds"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "If you want to have a meeting, sport race on a public road, you need permission from:",
    options: [
      "People living in the area",
      "Parks and gardens",
      "The traffic department and the police"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The traffic department and the police"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "How would you derive a 3 seconds following distance?",
    options: ["1, 2, 3", "1 and 1,1 and 2,1 and 3", "1001, 1002, 1003"],
    correctAnswer: "1001, 1002, 1003"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the stopping distance behind another vehicle?",
    options: ["4 metres or one vehicle length", "2 metres", "1.4 metres"],
    correctAnswer: "4 metres or one vehicle length"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "A double white line separated by a broken line means that:",
    options: [
      "No traffic may cross the solid lines for any reason",
      "You may cross to access property",
      "You may overtake if it is safe to do so"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "You may overtake if it is safe to do so"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "A 16 zag zone indicates which area?",
    options: [
      "Pedestrians have the right of way",
      "Slippery road",
      "Windy road ahead"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Pedestrians have the right of way"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the general speed limit for taxis outside an urban area?",
    options: ["90 km/h", "100 km/h", "80 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: "100 km/h"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the distance that your vehicle dim lights may hit the road surface in front of another vehicle?",
    options: ["45m", "150m", "100m"],
    correctAnswer: "45m"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the color of regulatory sign?",
    options: ["Red, white and black", "Blue and white", "Yellow and black"],
    correctAnswer: "Blue and white"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What colors are information boards on freeway?",
    options: ["Blue and white", "Green and white", "Brown and white"],
    correctAnswer: "Green and white"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "When you see sign i---you must:",
    options: [
      "Drive at the indicated speed or faster",
      "Drive slower than the speed indicated",
      "Drive faster than the speed indicated"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Drive slower than the speed indicated"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "The sign --- means:",
    options: ["Not less than 10 tons", "Not more than 10 tons", "Drive at 10km/h"],
    correctAnswer: "Not more than 10 tons"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Which vehicle shown in sign --- may drive here?",
    options: ["Taxis", "Motor vehicles", "Mini buses"],
    correctAnswer: "Motor vehicles"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What vehicles do the --- sign allow to enter?",
    options: ["Tradors", "Unauthorized vehicles", "Authorized vehicles"],
    correctAnswer: "Authorized vehicles"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "In sign --- says that you are forbid to use your hooter for how many metres?",
    options: [
      "100m beyond the sign",
      "500m beyond the sign",
      "30m beyond the sign"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "100m beyond the sign"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What may you legally do on a public road?",
    options: [
      "Pass another vehicle turning right on the left hand side without driving on the shoulder of the road",
      "Pass another vehicle at any place on the left hand side if it is turning right",
      "Not pass any vehicle on the left hand side"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Pass another vehicle at any place on the left hand side if it is turning right"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "When the vehicle behind you flashes his/her lights what do you do?",
    options: [
      "Move to the left as far as it is safe on another lane",
      "Do not move",
      "Give hand signs to pass"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Move to the left as far as it is safe on another lane"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What must you do if a vehicle wants to overtake you?",
    options: [
      "Slow down, use brakes if necessary and go to another lane",
      "Move over to the sidewalk to allow him pass",
      "Drive faster"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Slow down, use brakes if necessary and go to another lane"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What can you do on two solid lines divided by the white broken line?",
    options: ["Make a U-turn", "Access property", "Overtake"],
    correctAnswer: "Access property"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "When does a pedestrian have a right of way?",
    options: [
      "When they are crossing a pedestrian or at a zig zag zone",
      "When they have crossed half way through then the red man shows",
      "Both when they are crossing a pedestrian or at a zig zag zone and when they have crossed half way through then the red man shows"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Both when they are crossing a pedestrian or at a zig zag zone and when they have crossed half way through then the red man shows"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What must you do when you come to an intersection?",
    options: [
      "Turn while there are other vehicles turning",
      "Move in the sequence you have stopped",
      "Stop at the intersection, wait for traffic to clear then proceed"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Move in the sequence you have stopped"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Can you overtake a bus at a pedestrian crossing that is loaded with passengers?",
    options: ["Both", "Yes", "No"],
    correctAnswer: "No"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "How soon before you approach a stop or turn must you carry out observations?",
    options: [
      "At least 200m or 20 seconds before",
      "At least 500m or 30 seconds before",
      "At least 100m or 10 seconds before"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "At least 200m or 20 seconds before"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "How long is the vehicle disc valid for?",
    options: ["12 months", "24 months", "9 months"],
    correctAnswer: "12 months"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the maximum distance that goods may project to the rear of the vehicle? (Variant)",
    options: ["1.5 metres", "1.8 metres", "2 metres"],
    correctAnswer: "1.8 metres"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What are the rules for carrying passengers in a drawn vehicle? (Variant)",
    options: [
      "The drawn vehicle must be a semi-trailer",
      "The vehicles must not exceed a speed of 40km/h",
      "The drawn vehicle must be a trailer"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The drawn vehicle must be a trailer"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "When may you overtake on the left? (Variant)",
    options: [
      "When it is safe to do so, If the vehicle you are passing is turning right, On a one way urban road that is wide enough for two or more vehicles to drive abreast",
      "When a vehicle has stopped at a pedestrian crossing, On a curve, When approaching a hill",
      "When it is a straight road, When your view is not obstructed, If the space to the left of the edge line marking is open on a single lane road"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "When it is safe to do so, If the vehicle you are passing is turning right, On a one way urban road that is wide enough for two or more vehicles to drive abreast"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "These vehicles are allowed on a freeway: (Variant)",
    options: [
      "Motorcycles 50cc or less, Animal drawn vehicles, Special vehicles 230kg or less designed for disabled people",
      "Minibus, Heavy motor vehicles, Motorcycles 125cc or more",
      "Tractors doing freeway maintenance, Buses, Light motor vehicles"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Tractors doing freeway maintenance, Buses, Light motor vehicles"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "When a vehicle is being towed the driver must have: (Variant)",
    options: [
      "Efficient brakes",
      "Both efficient brakes and a licence of the same class vehicle that is being towed",
      "Have a licence of the same class vehicle that is being towed"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Both efficient brakes and a licence of the same class vehicle that is being towed"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "If you have learned you can: (Variant)",
    options: [
      "Both drive on the freeway with a licensed driver and carry passengers",
      "Drive on the freeway with a licensed driver",
      "Carry passengers"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Drive on the freeway with a licensed driver"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "The dipped beams of a motor vehicle should: (Variant)",
    options: [
      "Be used in urban areas, Be used in dense traffic",
      "Be used in rural area, Be used in dense traffic, Only be used when there is no approaching traffic",
      "Be used between sunrise and sunset, Be used on misty days, Strike the road surface not more than 150m ahead of the vehicle"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Be used in urban areas, Be used in dense traffic"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "Which of the following can be regarded as abandoned vehicles? (Variant)",
    options: [
      "A vehicle whose owner cannot be identified",
      "A vehicle that is parked illegally",
      "A vehicle that is likely to cause an obstruction"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A vehicle whose owner cannot be identified"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "When does a pedestrian have a right of way? (Variant)",
    options: [
      "When they are crossing a pedestrian crossing or at a zigzag zone",
      "When they have crossed half way through then the red man shows",
      "Both (a) and (b)"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "When they are crossing a pedestrian crossing or at a zigzag zone"
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What must you do when you come to an intersection? (Variant)",
    options: [
      "Turn while there are other vehicles turning",
      "Move in the sequence you have stopped",
      "Stop at the intersection, wait for traffic to clear then proceed."
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Stop at the intersection, wait for traffic to clear then proceed."
  },
  {
    category: "rules",
    question: "What is the distance that your vehicle dim lights may hit the road surface in front of another vehicle? (Variant)",
    options: ["45m", "150m", "100m"],
    correctAnswer: "150m"
  },
  {
  category: "rules",
  question: "A safe following distance is, when the vehicle in front of you suddenly stops, you could:",
  options: [
    "Swerve and stop next to it",
    "Stop without swerving",
    "Swerve and pass"
  ],
  correctAnswer: "Stop without swerving"
}
]